violence which are really useful data
for us because not only we get like your
private data trying to be there but
again
device itself or us those are way more
useful type of data that we can use the
function that we cannot with just that
and so yeah I mean that is that like as
you can see the tribe is very strong
before from multiple users likely and so
the amount of like good high definition
day that we that were interested in to
circulate and we respect we come to make
pretty much like insignificant the
amount of data that we actually get from
purely from the compromise like how how
scalable you want the system to be like
we said we plan to achieve one of the
media minds in like a year or something
more than something more than a year and
so this code the trade-off is between
how how defined how like how much data
you want to collect all sophisticated
you want to be a physical action caster
scalability and we believe that we found
kind of like the best sweet spot with
open pilot people driving with with our
dash cam with Iran with the unibody so
because you kind of connect all the data
we need
it's like scare what I'm untamable so
every company works on spaces their own
definition like the or definition of the
type of it'd be about our size pink
party impiety yes sorry I came only to
skip the zipper incident but it strikes
me that I think like tests these other
vehicles they have so many other sensors
they can be so much more aware of the
surrounding context so are you able to
read those from the canvas or you just
blow it off and go straight vision from
the camera how do you address that
because yeah well so not to make a
Suzanne this is a lot better than what
what should stay with the car step one
is like let's use as much as possible
what you see in front of you right you
can ever season and he's like a lot
better what is today using just what you
see in front of you right and there's a
good starting point which is what
provide however we can also read
everything it comes from your car so if
your car is a key for example we decided
a door so what we can read some
information from the side the other
story so we integrate with some that we
plant correctly
yeah but we do have access to the to the
other data so most of the consulship
today that are compatible with they are
equipped with adaptive cruise control
and so they already can tweet with arada
and we have used right now like the
account features so we do use as much as
possible what comes with the car and
then of course I certain point we do we
do believe that to expand the system and
to make the system like a more valuable
yeah you would need like mobile view
around the car but right now the
limitation is not really how much you
see is more like how when you use what
you can see OMS are taking measures to
improve the partition even security to
block exactly what open pilots trying to
do so how do you actually do that how do
you actually arranged yeah I mean open
pilots for us right now is it's a
development project and the way to make
up a palette scalable to have to engage
with a lot of like developers around the
world is to make a pilot what it is
today which is like a tool or software
that can work with can that people can
buy today the EM cover for karma he is
actually to engage with OEM of T one
supplier and work together to ship out
the pilot in their product in their cars
like assistant systems so if this is a
start for us it's not the end goal what
we have today is not yet gone their goal
is how to hope we hope we scale and the
only way to scale is engaging with oh
yeah it actually wants to wants to ship
do you think that you're gonna continue
with the windshield mounted device or is
it
I'm trying to cameras that are already
in the vehicle no you can't Fellini use
the camel sense of any of the names
because they're my kind of wire that
that actually we achieved it as imaging
processing so it's very hard to be the
images are Fox became
they go we right now we were okay like
using my camera provided by our systems
the camera itself is like she is not
like it makes nice and Barb and I don't
think it would refuse otherwise yes
yeah some came from me great thank you
do i you're welcome
do I have traits to get that data
absolutely somehow yes how is it
protected good question so you have
absolutely access to download your data
this is like something that we consider
a main use for developer terms like if
you are driving and you want to do some
test you want to collect data when you
should have access to your data you
should be able to know your data we like
to two to three weeks ago we released
all our most of some of the important
development tools that we use to develop
open files so that you can actually
develop the same in the same way that we
do and so you came to I collect it
downloaded it that you that you that you
actually collect and develop with
regarding the fish the driver facing
camera by default there's a table in
settings by default the table yourself
so we don't record your data we still
provide you the monitoring functionality
no we don't record your data if you want
to contribute and give us more like data
diversity which we actually need to
develop like a better system but you can
turn it on and then we have access to
your data
but be something to other
no absolutely have no you you can decide
to share the link to your data which is
like a generated thing not something
obvious with other with other people but
of course not like other people don't
have access to your data and we share
that data with other users
I think the only thing that we know
about the user is like their Google
login system so we don't we don't know
like any like personal informations
except
there's parts my question what is the
privacy question with the other point of
view
well if he falls release 33 hours of
data that you can download from our
website so that I think that answers
your question right so we have like
three of our data that we collected
driving and that's like open and
downloadable and we provided tools to
develop the data that we collect if you
believe it's useful to developers and of
course you have access to your data so
party of data MPAs that said that we
believe could be useful for people to
live out on which comes from our
personal life that is set as comma
Engineers
yeah
okay
no it's not actually we're still using
yes we are still saying it we're still
using it is the main device that we use
for interfacing with the card that you
guys have on the card which is sending
the autopilot to stielike device now we
don't plan to shift away from heater is
it's pretty I mean like the chip that is
using is not like the limit of what the
capability keeping the users that we do
absolutely no we still plan to stick
with it we plant a cone is called like
Panda is like the code is also open
source people ready contributed to it
and so the project by itself
yeah we don't want to bring in to an end
at all like anytime soon so it's the
driver
cool I well thank you guys so much um we
have a merch table if you're interested
in buying either a self-driving car tour
t-shirt or any of the devices that
Ricardo mentioned will be around Eddie
Harold myself Ricardo if you guys want
to chat with us ask other questions what
the price tags